Guide to the Nancy Hanks Papers, 1894-1987 (bulk 1945-1983)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- National Endowment for the Arts Series, 1965-1982and undated(bulk 1969-1977) (47 boxes)
  - Office Files
    - Inaugural Committee Cultural Events, 1976-1977 (Box 51)
    - Jefferson Award and Speech, 1977 (Box 51)
    - Labor/Management Relationship in the Arts, 1975-1977 (Box 51)
    - Literature, 1972, 1976-1977 (Box 51)
    - Livable Cities Program, 1977-1978 (Box 51)
    - Media/Arts Information Project, 1976-1977 (Box 51)
    - Miami's Expansion Arts Program, 1975 (Box 51)
    - Mondale, Joan, 1977 (Box 51)
    - Museum Indemnity Act, 1975 (Box 51)
    - Museums, 1976-1977 (Box 51)
    - Music, 1975, 1977 (Box 51)
    - National Bicentennial Photography Project, 1975 (Box 51)
    - A National Corporate Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 51)
    - National Executive Service Corps, 1977 (Box 52)
    - National Festival of the Arts, 1977 (Box 52)
    - National Report on the Arts, 1975 (Box 52)
    - New Jersey State Council on the Arts, 1975-1976 (Box 52)
    - New York State Council's Formula Funding, 1976 (Box 52)
    - Notebook, 1969 (Box 52)
    - OPERA America, 1977 (Box 52)
    - Outreach Programs, 1974-1975 (Box 52)
    - Panel Selection, 1972-1975 (Box 52)
    - Personnel, 1971-1975, undated, (2 folders) (Box 52)
    - Photography/Film Project, 1975-1977 (Box 53)
    - Presidential Resolution, 1976 (Box 53)
    - President's Commission on Mental Health, 1977 (Box 53)
    - Press Releases, 1969-1977 and undated (Box 53)
    - Program Directors' Meetings, 1975 (Box 53)
    - Programming in the Arts, 1977 (Box 53)
    - Public Media Program, 1972, 1975-1976 (Box 53)
    - Public Radio, 1976 (Box 53)
    - Public Service Awards, 1977 (Box 53)
    - Reappointment, 1969-1973, 1977 (Box 53)
    - Reauthorization, 1975-1976 (Box 53)
    - Reorganization of N.E.A., 1977 (Box 53)
    - Resumés, 1976 (Box 54)
    - Scrapbook, 1970, 1977, (2 folders) (Box 54)
    - Shared Opera Productions, 1975-1977, (2 folders) (Box 54)
    - Small Groups, 1977 (Box 54)
    - Special Projects, 1970-1977, undated, (2 folders) (Box 54)
    - Special Projects Office, 1976 (Box 54)
    - Spoleto Festival, 1977 (Box 54)
    - Star Track: An automated Spotlight Control System, 1975 (Box 55)
    - State Arts Agencies, 1975-1977 (Box 55)
    - State Arts Councils, 1977 (Box 55)
    - Stover, Carl E., Summary Activity Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 55)
    - Support the Arts Program, 1977 Mar.-June 1-16, (3 folders) (Box 55)
    - Support the Arts Program, 1977 June17-30 - Oct., (2 folders) (Box 56)
    - Symphony Orchestras, 1976-1977 (Box 56)
    - Task Force on Policies and Operations--Report, 1973 (Box 56)
    - Task Forces, 1977 (Box 56)
    - Task Force on The Education, Training and Development of Professional Artists and Arts Educators, 1977 (Box 56)
    - Taxation and Art, 1977 (Box 56)
    - "Ten Years for Tomorrow," Pts. 1-2, 1975, (2 folders) (Box 56)
    - "Ten Years for Tomorrow," Pts. 2-3, 1975, (5 folders) (Box 57)
    - Theatre, 1972-1977, (2 folders) (Box 57)
    - Theatre, 1978 (Box 58)
    - Theatre Panel Meeting, 1971, Apr. 27-28 (Box 58)
    - A Tourism Plan for New York, 1977 (Box 58)
    - Transition, 1976-1977, (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, 1975-1978 (Box 58)
    - Van Cliburn Competition, 1977 (Box 58)
    - Vice President's Residence, 1977 (Box 58)
    - "Visions" - TV's Original Plays for Public TV, 1976 (Box 58)
    - Visual Arts, 1976-1977 (Box 59)
    - White House, 1975-1977 (Box 59)
    - White House Christmas Tree, 1975-1976 (Box 59)
    - Winston-Salem Arts Council, 1976-1977 (Box 59)
    - Writings, 1970-1976, undated (Box 59)
  - Speeches
    - List, 1970-1975 (Box 59)
    - 1969-1970 Dec., (3 folders) (Box 59)
    - 1971 Jan.-1972 Feb., (5 folders) (Box 69)
    - 1972 Mar.-1973 Mar., (4 folders) (Box 61)
    - 1973 Apr.-1974 Dec., (5 folders) (Box 62)
    - 1975 Jan.-1975 Dec., (5 folders) (Box 63)
    - 1976 Jan.-June, (4 folders, 1 video cassette tape) (Box 64)
    - 1976 July-1977 Sept., (4 folders) (Box 65)
    - Incomplete and/or undated (Box 65)
  - Telephone Records
    - 1971 July-1972 Dec., (5 folders) (Box 66)
    - Telephone Records, 1973-1974, A-B (Box 66)
    - 1973-1974, C-Q, (6 folders) (Box 67)
    - 1973-1974, R-Z, (4 folders) (Box 68)
    - 1975, (A-L, (4 folders) (Box 68)
    - 1975, M-Z, (4 folders) (Box 69)
    - 1976, A-H, (3 folders) (Box 69)
    - 1976, I-Z, (5 folders) (Box 70)
    - 1977, A-G, (2 folders) (Box 70)
    - 1977, H-Z, (4 folders) (Box 71)
  - Trips
    - List, 1970-1974 (Box 71)
    - Europe, 1971 (Box 71)
    - Sweden/Finland, 1973 (Box 71)
    - Winston-Salem, NC; Jackson, MS., Louisville, KY. 1974 Sept., (3 folders) (Box 71)
    - Durham, NC, 1974 Oct. (Box 72)
    - Columbia, SC, 1974 Nov. (Box 72)
    - Alaska; California; Philadelphia, 1975 Mar., (3 folders) (Box 72)
    - Lubbock, TX; New York; Washington, DC; New Brunswick, NJ, 1975 Apr., (4 folders) (Box 72)
    - Seattle, WA, 1975 Apr./May (Box 72)
    - South Bend, IN, 1975 May (Box 72)
    - Amherst, Boston, MA, 1975 May/June (Box 72)
    - Cleveland, 1975 July (Box 72)
    - New York, NY, 1975 Dec. (Box 72)
    - Richmond, VA, 1976 Jan. (Box 73)
    - Philadelphia, 1976 Apr. (Box 73)
    - Washington, DC; Boston, 1976 June, (2 folders) (Box 73)
    - Allentown, PA; New York, NY; College Park, MD, 1977 May, (3 folders) (Box 73)
    - Washington, 1977 June (Box 73)
    - San Antonio, TX, 1977 Sept./Oct. (Box 73)
  - Post-Chairmanship
    - 1977-1978 Sept. (Box 73)
    - 1978 Oct.-1980 Oct., (4 folders) (Box 73)
    - 1980 Nov.-1981 Nov., (8 folders) (Box 74)
    - 1981 Nov.-1982 Nov. undated, (5 folders) (Box 75)
    - Edward Banfield Manuscript, 1980-1981, (2 folders) (Box 75)
    - Correspondence: 1980-1982, undated (Box 75)
    - Parties, 1978-1982 (Box 75)
  - Miscellaneous
    - 1969-1977, undated, (2 folders) (Box 76)
- Rockefeller Brothers Fund Series, 1965-1983and undated(bulk 1977-1983) (6 boxes).
  Records Hanks' involvement in the organization after her tenure at NEA, and includes information on arts organizations and the Rockefeller brothers: John D., 3d; Laurance S.; and Nelson. Includes typed, printed, and mimeographed material; correspondence; clippings; and telephone records. Arranged alphabetically by organization, topic, or person.
  - Alcoholics (Alcohol and Drugs), 1982 July (Box 76)
  - The American Ditchley Foundation, 1978-1982 (Box 76)
  - Articles by or about associates of interest to Nancy Hanks, 1979 (Box 76)
  - Arts International, 1978-1982 (Box 76)
  - Awards, 1981-1982, undated (Box 76)
  - Bluhdorn, Charles, 1981 (Box 76)
  - Business Committee for the Arts, 1981 (Box 76)
  - Catalyst, 1979-1981 (Box 76)
  - Chicago Lyric Opera and Robert Leys, 1980-1982, undated (Box 77)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1981 (Box 77)
  - Columbia University Centennial, 1980 (Box 77)
  - The Conservation Foundation, 1980 (Box 77)
  - Contributions: Rockefeller Memorial Fund, 1979-1980 (Box 77)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 77)
  - Dartmouth College, Rockefeller Center for the Social Sciences, 1980-1981 (Box 77)
  - Erick Hawkins Dance Company, 1978-1983, undated (Box 77)
  - Grants, 1977-1982, undated (Box 77)
  - Gulf and Western (Levinson), 1978-1981 (Box 77)
  - Hudson River Valley Project, 1982 (Box 77)
  - The Institute for Art and Urban Resources, Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 77)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc., 1977-1981 (Box 77)
  - Japan Society Seventy-Fifth Anniversary Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 78)
  - Bob Kingston, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
  - Lacy, Bill, 1979-1982 (Box 78)
  - Lincoln Center, 1978-1981 (Box 78)
  - MacDowell Colony, 1979-1981 (Box 78)
  - Mannes College of Music, 1981-1982 (Box 78)
  - Meetings, 1980 (Box 78)
  - Michigan Artrain, 1979-1982 (Box 78)
  - Miscellaneous, 1977-1982, undated (Box 78)
  - National Council on the Arts--Past Members, 1977-1982 (Box 78)
  - Notecards, 1979-1982, undated (Box 78)
  - Planning and Review; Annual Report, 1977-1980, undated (Box 78)
  - Pocantico; Kykuit, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
  - Portfolio Magazine, 1977-1981, undated (Box 79)
  - Proposals, 1978-1982, undated, (3 folders) (Box 79)
  - Public Benefit Corporation, 1981 June (Box 79)
  - Puerto Rican Travelling Theatre, 1978-1981 (Box 79)
  - Requests and/or Invitations Declined, 1978-1981, undated (Box 79)
  - Resumés, 1978-1980 Feb. (Box 79)
  - Resumés, 1980 Mar.-1982, undated (Box 80)
  - Rockefeller Farm, 1981 (Box 80)
  - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd, 1978 (Box 80)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1975-1983, undated (2 folders) (Box 80)
  - Rockefeller (Nelson) Collection, 1978-1979, undated (Box 80)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.:
    - Memorial Fund for the New York College of Osteopathic Medicine, 1978-1982, undated (Box 80)
    - Memorial Service, 1978-1982, undated (Box 80)
    - Miscellaneous, 1978-1982 (Box 80)
  - Special Studies Project, 1968 (Box 80)
  - Speeches, 1977-1978, undated (Box 80)
  - Speeches: (Box 81)
    - Background Material, 1976-1982, undated (Box 81)
    - Delivered by others on topics of interest to Nancy Hanks, 1978-1981 (Box 81)
  - Telephone Records, 1977-1982, (3 folders) (Box 81)
- Personal Series, 1927-1983and undated(bulk 1940s-1970s)(59 boxes).
  The largest series, it includes mimeographed, printed, and typed material; correspondence and memoranda; telephone records; calendars; clippings (biographical information about Hanks); resumes; and trips information. Major categories are the alphabetical files, chiefly 1970sand 1980s,(arranged by topic) and correspondence (arranged alphabetically by correspondent's surname, then chronologically). Other categories include financial papers, scrapbooks, speeches, and student papers (chiefly high school and college). Financial papers include bank records, medical bills, expenses and contributions such as to the National Republican Senatorial Committee, tax returns, stock certificates and information, and real estate papers. Arranged alphabetically by topic. Includes a small amount of restricted material at the end.
  - Alphabetical Files
    - Address file, undated (Box 81)
    - Addresses and telephone numbers, 1976-1977, undated (Box 81)
    - The American Assembly, 1977 (Box 81)
    - American Association of Museums Council, 1974-1982, undated (Box 82)
    - American Institute of Architects, 1979-1982 (Box 82)
    - Ancestry, 1969-1977 (Box 82)
    - Anderson, Walter, 1982 (Box 82)
    - Andrew Mellon Collection, National Gallery of Art, Film transcript, undated (Box 82)
    - Arena Stage, 1980, undated (Box 82)
    - Art, 1980-1981, undated (Box 82)
    - Arts in Education, 1978-1982 (Box 82)
    - Arts International, 1980-1982, undated (Box 82)
    - Associated Councils of the Arts, 1971-1980 (Box 82)
    - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1981-1982 (Box 82)
    - Audio-visual:Cassette tapes, 1977
      - Transcript, undated (Box 82)
    - Audiovisual (General), undated (Box 83)
    - Autobiographical article, Lynn Gilbert, 1981, undated (Box 83)
    - Automobiles, 1941-1982 (Box 83)
    - Awards in the Visual Arts, 1979-1980 (Box 83)
    - Awards in the Visual Arts: 1980-1983, undated, (2 folders) (Box 84)
    - Baber, Alice, 1982, undated (Box 84)
    - Battersby, Jean, 1981 (Box 84)
    - Benedict, Steve, 1978-1980, undated (Box 84)
    - Biographical information, 1958-1977 (Box 84)
    - Birth cards, 1927 (Box 84)
    - Booth, John, 1981-1982 (Box 85)
    - Brandywine Conservancy, 1979-1981, undated (Box 85)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music, 1979 (Box 85)
    - Calendars, 1953-1974, (4 folders) (Box 85)
    - Calendars, 1975-1982, (4 folders) (Box 86)
    - Cards, 1967-1981, undated (Box 86)
    - Cashiers, N.C., 1982 (Box 86)
    - Catalyst awards, 1978-1982 (Box 86)
    - Center for Arts information, 1980 (Box 86)
    - Clippings, 1934-1986, undated (Box 86)
    - Columbia University, 1979-1980 (Box 87)
    - Committee to Fight Inflation, 1980 (Box 87)
    - Commission on Museums for a New Century, 1981-1982, (6 folders) (Box 87)
    - Congressional Arts Caucus, 1981 (Box 87)
    - Conoco:
      - Board and committee material, and board trips, 1978-1982 (Box 87)
      - Continental oil, 1957-1981, undated (Box 87)
      - Corporate contributions, films, 1979-1982 (Box 87)
    - Conoco Inc., Du Pont Merger, 1981 (Box 87)
    - Conoco: (Box 88)
      - Miscellaneous, 1979-1982, undated (Box 88)
      - Special meeting of the Board of Directors, 1981 May (Box 88)
      - U.S. Board Trip, 1980 Oct. (Box 88)
    - The Conservation Foundation, 1978-1982, undated, (2 folders) (Box 88)
    - Corporation for Older Americans, 1980-1982 (Box 88)
    - Cosmopolitan Club, 1969-1979, undated (Box 88)
    - Council on Foundations, Inc.: Summary of selected decisions..., 1977 (Box 88)
    - Council on Foundations, 1977-1978 (Box 89)
    - Cultural Resources, 1979, undated (Box 89)
    - Davis, Hal: Memorial Symphony programs, 1978, undated (Box 89)
    - The Discovery: Five Centuries, 1982 (Box 89)
    - Ditchley Foundations, 1978-1982 (Box 89)
    - Geraldine R. Dodge Foundation, 1980 (Box 89)
    - Equitable Life Insurance Society of the United States (ELAS):
      - Age Discrimination Lawsuit, 1982 (Box 89)
      - Arts Acquisition Policy, 1982 (Box 89)
      - Board: Committee material, 1978-1980 (Box 89)
      - Board of Directors meetings, related materials, community luncheon, 1980-1982 (Box 89)
    - Equitable Life Insurance Society of the United States (ELAS): (Box 90)
      - Board of Directors, Meetings, Related materials, 1982 (Nov.-Dec.) (Box 90)
      - Contributions, subcommittees, 1978-1982 (Box 90)
      - Directors' forms, 1978-1982 (Box 90)
      - Harris, Dave, 1982 (Box 90)
      - Public Relations, insurance plans, letters from policyholders, 1978-1983 (Box 90)
      - Real estate, travel, money market prospectus, miscellaneous, 1970-1982 (Box 90)
      - Report to board of directors, 1981 July (Box 90)
      - Securities reports, 1978-1981 (Box 90)
    - Ellis Island, 1981-1982 (Box 90)
    - Employment--Washington and New York, 1949-1958 (Box 90)
    - Estate, disposition of, 1979-1985, (2 folders) (Box 91)
    - Federal City Council, 1971-1977 (Box 91)
    - Focus magazine article, 1980 (Box 91)
    - Folklife Center, 1977-1979 (Box 91)
    - Ford, Oneil, 1980-1982 (Box 91)
    - Friends, 1976-1980 (Box 91)
    - Fundraising, Personnel, 1979 (Box 91)
    - Getty Museum, 1982 (Box 91)
    - Gilbert, Lynn, 1979-1981 (Box 91)
    - Hanes, Phil, 1978-1981, undated (Box 92)
    - Hanks/Weems/Cayce Family, 1964-1969, undated (Box 92)
    - Health Headways (Eileen Growald, Barry Flint), 1982 (Box 92)
    - Hillwood Museum, 1981 (Box 92)
    - Honorary Degrees and Awards, 1979-1982 (Box 92)
    - Honory degree, University of Florida, 1979 (Box 92)
    - Honors/Positions Declined, 1973-1982 (Box 92)
    - Inaugural Activities Information, 1973 (Box 92)
    - Independent sector, 1980-1982, (2 folders) (Box 92)
    - Indo-U.S. Subcommission on Education and Culture (Meetings), 1975-1977 (Box 92)
    - Indo-U.S. Subcommission on Education and Culture (Meetings), 1975-1977 (Box 93)
    - Indo-U.S. Subcommission on Education and Culture, 1975-1981, (6 folders) (Box 93)
    - Indo-U.S. Commission on Education and Culture, 1982 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 94)
    - Indo-U.S. Subcommission on Education and Culture: Museum Committee, 1978-1982 (Box 94)
    - Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1981 (Box 94)
    - Interests, 1977-1983 (Box 94)
    - Invitations, 1953-1980, undated (Box 94)
    - Junior Council of the Museum of Modern Art, 1981 (Box 94)
    - Leeper, Doris, 1978-1982 (Box 94)
    - Legal papers, 1956-1968 (Box 94)
    - Leys, Robert, 1978 (Box 94)
    - MacDowell Colony, 1979-1981, undated (Box 94)
    - MacFolly Records, 1969-1982 (Box 94)
    - Mayleas, Ruth, 1980-1981, undated (Box 94)
    - Mayor's Arts Awards, 1981-1982, undated, (2 folders) (Box 95)
    - Memberships held by Nancy Hanks, 1966-1982 (Box 95)
    - Memorials and Tributes, 1983 (Box 95)
    - National Assembly of State Arts Agencies, 1981 (Box 95)
    - National Academy of Public Administration, 1979-1983, (2 folders) (Box 95)
    - National Artists Fellowship Program, 1980, undated (Box 96)
    - The National Center for Citizen Involvement, 1980-1981 (Box 96)
    - National Collection of Fine Arts, 1979 (Box 96)
    - National Committee for Urban Recreation, 1978-1982, undated (Box 96)
    - National Council of Arts Administrators Award, 1981 (Box 96)
    - National Council on the Arts, 1977-1978 (Box 96)
    - National Executive Service Corps, 1978-1979 (Box 96)
    - National Museum of American Art, 1981, undated (Box 96)
    - National Museum of the Building Arts, 1980-1981 (Box 96)
    - National Museum of Women's Art, 1982 (Box 96)
    - New York Botanical Gardens, 1982 (Box 96)
    - North Carolina Museum of Art, 1977-1982 (Box 96)
    - North Carolina Museum of Art (Meeting), 1978-1979 (Box 96)
    - Office of Defense Mobilization, 1951-1952 (Box 96)
    - Old Post Office, 1977-1982 (Box 96)
    - Ossabaw Foundation, 1981-1982, undated (Box 96)
    - Paintings, 1971-1982 (Box 96)
    - Parties: (Box 97)
      - 1977-1982, undated (Box 97)
      - Prince, Joe; Menke, Marj, 1978 (Box 97)
      - Randolpf, Len, 1982, undated (Box 97)
      - Reger, Lawrence, 1978 (Box 97)
      - Thanksgiving, 1982 (Box 97)
      - White, Jenny, 1982 (Box 97)
      - Partners for Livable Places, 1978-1982 and n.d, (3 folders) (Box 97)
    - Phillips Collection, 1978-1982, undated, (3 folders) (Box 98)
    - Playbills of Performances Attended, 1957-1982, undated, (3 folders) (Box 98)
    - Presidential Task Force on the Arts and Humanities: (Box 99)
      - Correspondence, 1981-1982, undated (Box 99)
      - Meetings and reports, 1981, (3 folders) (Box 99)
    - Presidential Task Force on the Arts and Humanities: Meetings and reports, 1981-1982 and undated, (4 folders) (Box 100)
    - President's Committee on the Arts and Humanities, 1976-1982, undated (Box 100)
    - Princeton Art Museum, 1980-1981, undated (Box 100)
    - Princeton Club, N.Y., 1979, undated (Box 100)
    - Randolf, Len, 1980-1982 (Box 100)
    - Resumés, requests, and recommendations, 1977, Oct.-1978 (Box 100)
    - Resumés, requests, and recommendations, 1979 Jan.-1982 April, (7 folders) (Box 101)
    - Resumés, requests, and recommendations, 1982 May-1983 Jan., undated (Box 102)
    - Reunions:
      - Duke, 1979, undated (Box 102)
      - Godchildren, 1981-1982 (Box 102)
    - Robert College of Istanbul, 1970-1972, (2 folders) (Box 102)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Panel Report II, 1958 (Box 102)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson, A., 1954-1965, undated (Box 102)
    - Rockefeller Panel Reports Tenth Anniversary, 1975 (Box 102)
    - Russell, Rosalind Arthritis Center, 1980-1981 (Box 103)
    - Salzburg Seminar, 1977-1982, undated, (3 folders) (Box 103)
    - Sanders, Don, 1974-1977 (Box 103)
    - Schmerz, Monique, 1980-1981 (Box 103)
    - Scholastic, Inc., 1980-1981 Mar., (2 folders) (Box 103)
    - Scholastic, Inc., 1981 Apr.-1982, (4 folders) (Box 104)
    - Small Museums, 1981-1982, undated (Box 104)
    - Smithsonian Institution: Board of Regents, 1981-1982, (3 folders) (Box 104)
    - Smithsonian Institution: Board of Regents, 1982 (Box 105)
    - Southeast Seven IV, undated (Box 105)
    - Souvenirs, 1969-1973, 1976, undated (Box 105)
    - Stover, Carl, 1979-1982 (Box 105)
    - Straight, Michael, 1979-1981 (Box 105)
    - Sweet Briar, 1978-1979, undated (Box 105)
    - Taylor, Joshua C., 1981-1982 (Box 105)
    - Telephone Records, 1977-1980, (2 folders) (Box 105)
    - Telephone Records, 1981-1982, undated (Box 106)
    - Trans County Cable, 1980-1982 (Box 106)
    - Trips:
      - United Kingdom, France, 1948 (Box 106)
      - Europe, 1955 (Box 106)
      - Notebook, 1958-1961 (Box 106)
      - World trip, 1961 (Box 106)
      - Greece, 1970 (Box 106)
      - India, London, U.S., 1978 (Box 106)
      - Denver, 1979 (Box 106)
      - USSR, 1982 (Box 106)
      - Passports and documents, 1948-1982 (Box 106)
      - Miscellaneous, 1963-1981, undated (Box 106)
    - Van Cliburn: The Rildia Bee O'Bryan Cliburn Foundation, 1982 (Box 107)
    - Volunteer, 1980-1981 (Box 107)
    - University of Wisconsin, 1979-1980 (Box 107)
    - Wallet cards, 1948-1980, undated (Box 107)
    - White House Conference on Aging, 1980-1982, undated (Box 107)
    - Williams, Jeff, 1982 (Box 107)
    - Wolftrap Foundation, 1982 (Box 107)
    - Woodstock Conservancy, 1980-1982 (Box 107)
    - Yale University Program on Non-Profit Organizations, 1978-1982 (Box 107)
  - Correspondence
    - A, 1948-1982, undated (Box 107)
    - Allen, Julia, 1955-1959 (Box 108)
    - B, 1946-1983, undated, (4 folders) (Box 108)
    - Blackham, Bobbie and Bill, 1949-1966 (Box 108)
    - C, 1945-1982, undated, (2 folders) (Box 108)
    - Carpenter, William A., 1946 July-1947 Apr., (6 folders) (Box 109)
    - Carpenter, William A., 1947 May-1949, (3 folders) (Box 110)
    - Cleland, James T., 1949-1969 (Box 110)
    - Corl, William T. and Lynn, 1945-1960 (Box 110)
    - Creel, Jane and Dana, 1961-1966 (Box 110)
    - Coyne, J. William, 1948-1960 (Box 110)
    - D, 1945-1982, undated (Box 110)
    - E, 1954-1982, undated (Box 110)
    - F, 1945-1982 (Box 111)
    - Farrer, William, 1948-1950 (Box 111)
    - Fike, Edward L., 1950 (Box 111)
    - G, 1946-1986, undated (Box 111)
    - Gavs, David, 1948-1949 (Box 111)
    - Goldwater, Barry, 1964-1971 (Box 111)
    - Goodloe, Al, 1945-1949 (Box 111)
    - H, 1948-1976, undated, (2 folders) (Box 111)
    - H, 1977-1982, undated (Box 112)
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1935-1951 May, (5 folders) (Box 112)
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1951 June-1953 April, (5 folders) (Box 113)
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1953 May-1955 April, (6 folders) (Box 114)
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1955 May-Oct., (2 folders) (Box 115)
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1955 Nov.-1957 April, (6 folders) (Box 116)
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1957 May-1958 July, (5 folders) (Box 117)
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1958 Aug.-1959 Dec., (5 folders) (Box 118)
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1960 Jan.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 119)
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1961 Jan.-1963 Nov., undated, (5 folders) (Box 120)
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1964 Jan.-1969 Aug., (6 folders) (Box 121)
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1969 Sept.-1971 Oct., (6 folders) (Box 122)
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1971 Nov.-1978 June, undated, (5 folders) (Box 123)
    - Harris, Paul, 1948-1949 (Box 124)
    - I, 1972-1982, undated (Box 124)
    - J, 1950-1982, undated (Box 124)
    - Jennings, Richard G., 1949-1975 (Box 124)
    - Jones, Ruth, 1955-1959, undated (Box 124)
    - K, 1945-1981, undated, (2 folders) (Box 124)
    - Kennedy, Johy Royer, 1959-1974 (Box 124)
    - Kissinger, Henry A and family, 1958-1973, n.d (Box 124)
    - L, 1945-1982, undated, (2 folders) (Box 124)
    - Lurton, Nelson, 1946-1948, undated (Box 124)
    - Lynn, Richard, 1949-1950 (Box 124)
    - M, 1945-1983, undated, (4 folders) (Box 125)
    - Mitchell, Donna, 1957-1970, undated (Box 125)
    - Moore, Virginia, 1949-1950 (Box 125)
    - N, 1957-1981, undated (Box 125)
    - O, 1957-1975, undated (Box 125)
    - P, 1945-1982, undated (Box 125)
    - Parker, Kathleen and family, 1956-1961, undated (Box 126)
    - Paulsen, Don, 1945 (Box 126)
    - Persons, Elizabeth and Jack, 1949-1968 (Box 126)
    - Q-R, 1945-1982, undated, (2 folders) (Box 126)
    - Reid, Louis, 1955-1961 (Box 126)
    - Riggs, Polly and family, 1959-1977, undated (Box 126)
    - Robinson, Mary, 1948-1970, undated (Box 126)
    - Rockefeller family (Mary and Laurance Winthrop, Steven, Nelson, John D., 1948-1982 (Box 126)
    - Rutledge, Jay, 1948-1960, undated (Box 126)
    - S, 1945-1982, undated, (3 folders) (Box 127)